Please keep your virus definitions up-to-date. If possible, go to 'Settings' tab from WardWiz UI and enable the option 'Auto live update' to download new virus definitions to your computer.
Do not open any files attached to an email unless you know what it is, even if it appears to be received from a friend or someone you know. Some viruses can replicate themselves and spread through email. Confirm that your contact really sent an attachment.
Do not conduct on-line financial transactions from a public computer or wireless network. Doing your on-line banking, paying your bills, or shopping on-line on a publicly used computer or wireless network puts the privacy of your personal information at risk. So, save on-line financial transactions for your personal computer while using a trusted, secure wireless network.
Always create strong passwords that contains at least 8 characters with capital and lower-case letters, numbers and special characters to ensure the highest level of computer security. The more random the password, the better. Be sure to avoid passwords based on personal information or common patterns or sequences.